Guide to the Archives of Irish America County Societies Collection AIA.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- XI. Fermanagh, 1903-2001
  - Members and Mailing Lists, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - New York Irish History Roundtable article, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Notes - Director John G. Gilroy, 1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - St. Mary's Pipe Band, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parades, 1986-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Souvenir Journal Advertising, 1985-1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1989, 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 4, Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Digital media (floppy disk, unlabeled), undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- XII. Galway, 1932-2006
  - Galway Association of New York, Inc. 125th Anniversary Celebration and Banquet, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Galway Association of New York, Inc. Annual St. Patrick's Day Dinner-Dance, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Galway Association of New York, Inc. Annual St. Patrick's Day Dinner-Dance, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Galway Association of New York, Inc. Annual St. Patrick's Day Dinner-Dance, 2002, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Galway Association of New York, Inc. Remembrance of Colonel Patrick Kelly, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Galway Cathedral Fund Gala Benefit Ball, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Combined Galway Club of New York Testimonial Dinner: Galway Champion Football Team of 1956, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Galway Golf Society: 1st Galway Memorial Golf Outing, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hurling Club of New York Irish Tour, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Hurling Club of New York Dinner Dance Programs, 1972, 1980, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hurling Club of New York Dinner Dance Journals, 1985, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Hurling Club Photographs, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Men's Association Annual Banquet, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Men's Association Centennial Address: Cardinal Cook, Oct 24, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Men's Association Attendance Book, 1971-1995 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Men's Association Membership Ledger, circa 1950-1989 (Box 33)
  - Men's Association Minute Book, Jul 1916-Dec 1926; cuid811 (Box 34)
  - Men's Association Minute Book, Jan 1927-1928; cuid812 (Box 35)
  - Men's Association Minute Book, 1933-1951; cuid813 (Box 36)
  - Men's Association Minute Book, 1951-1957; cuid814 (Box 37)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association Annual Ball, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association Annual Ball, 1971-1973 (Box 5a, Folder 1)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association Annual Ball; Bicentennial Dinner Dance, 1974-1976 (Box 5a, Folder 2)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association Auditor's Report, Jan 1, 1957-Apr 30, 1957 (Box 5a, Folder 3)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association Centennial Celebration and Banquet, 1981 (Box 5a, Folder 4)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association Letterhead/Stationery, undated (Box 5a, Folder 5)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association -- Meetings and Event Ephemera, 1923-1956 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1942-1957 (Box 5a, Folder 6)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance Centennial, 1977-1980 (Box 5a, Folder 7)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance Split Club, 1981 (Box 5a, Folder 8)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1983-1984 (Box 5a, Folder 9)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1985 (Box 5a, Folder 10)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1986 (Box 5a, Folder 11)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1987 (Box 5a, Folder 12)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1988 (Box 5a, Folder 13)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1989 (Box 5a, Folder 14)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1990 (Box 5a, Folder 15)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association Testimonial Dinner, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Micael Moran J. R. A. Club St. Patrick's Night Galway Ball, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- XIII. Kerry, 1959-1997
  - Constitution and By-laws -- Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association, Kerry Ladies Benevolent Association, 1924-1974 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Ephemera, History, 1933-1964 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - John Farrel Testimonial Dinner, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gaelic Football Club of New York Annual Dinner Dance, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gaelic Football Club of New York Annual Dinner Dance, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association, 1994, 1997, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association: Administrative Records, 1962, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 7, Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association All-Ireland Football Champion Banquet, 1959, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association Annual Dinner Dance, 1984, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association minute book, 1903-1907; cuid13386
    Existence and Location of Originals
    The original minute book is in the possession of the Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association.
  - Ladies Auxiliary Costume, undated (Box 25)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Costume -- Cap, Cape, Skirt, undated (Box 66)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Costume -- Sweater, undated (Box 67)
- XIV. Kildare
  - Dinner Dane Programs and Flyers, 1996-2009 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- XV. Kilkenny (Kilkenny Men's Social and Benevolent Association), 1906-1993
  - Allied Irish Bank: Corporate Resolution, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Allied Irish Bank: Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Allied Irish Bank: Statements, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Allied Irish Bank: Statements, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Allied Irish Bank: Statements, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Annual Ball and Dinner-Dance: Correspondence and Circulars, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Annual Ball and Dinner Dance Programs, 1973-1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Annual Dinner Dance Tickets, 1974-1977, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Bills and Expenses, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cash Book, 1977-1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Constitution, after 1903 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Diamond Jubilee Banquet, April 29, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Dinner Dance, 1984, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Dinner Dance Finances, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dinner and Formal Rough Sheets, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gaelic Athletic Association, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Golden Jubilee Banquet, Oct 31, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hurling Club of New York, 1974-1993, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Incorporation Documents, 1903, 1906-1954, circa 1970-1979 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS) Audit, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Ledger Book, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Mialing Address Lists and Mailings to Members, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Membership Cards; Information on Members, 1980-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Membership Dues Ledger (photocopy), 1965-1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Memorial Society; Plot Improvement Fund, 1976-1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Minutes (photocopies of ledger book pages), 1970-1975; cuid815 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Newsletters, 1959-1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Newsletters and Announcements, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Photograph: Kilkenny Association of New York St Patrick's Day Festival Dance, Feb 24, 1962 (Box Shared Tamiment AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
  - Public Speeches and Statements, 1974-1984 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Union Dime Savings Bank: Statements, 1970-1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Reports (Box 8, Folder 6)
- XVI. Laois/Leix, 1973-1976
  - Calvary and Allied Cemeteries, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Leix Gaelic Football and Hurling Club Annual Dinner Dance, 1973, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Leix Junior Hurling Championship Medal, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Leix Men's Social & Benevolent Society, Inc. -- Certificates, 1934, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Leix Men's Social & Benevolent Society, Inc. -- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1969-1981 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Queens County Ireland Social and Benevolent Society of New York: Minutes, 1895-1909 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Queens County Ireland Social and Benevolent Society of New York: Membership, 1895-1919 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- XVII. Leitrim, 1915-2001
  - 86th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 101st Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 102nd Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 103rd Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 105th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 106th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 109th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 109th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 113th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - A Century of Leitrim Football in New York, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Carrick-on-Shannon Co. Leitrim Historical Society Famine Memorial Drawing, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - County Leitrim Men's Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association -- Certificate of Incorporation, 1910 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - County Leitrim Society Annual Ball, Grand Ball, Lotteries, 1965-1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - County Leitrim Society Centennial Year, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - County Leitrim Society Centennial Year Dinner Dance Program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - County Leitrim Society of New York -- Correspondence, 1984, 1990-1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - County Leitrim Society of New York -- Dinner Dance, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - John Joe McGirl Memorial, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Leitrim Young Men's Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association Ball/Benefit Social, 1915, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Map, undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Panoramic Photograph: Saint Patrick's Ball, County Letrim S & A Club, Palm Garden, Mar 16, 1946 (Box Shared Tamiment AIAXOS001, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1989, undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Saint Patrick's Day, 1941, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Sean Mac Diarmada Memorial Mass, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- XVIII. Limerick, 1990-1999
  - Hurling Club of New York Victory Celebration Dance, 1995, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Men's Benevolent and Social Assocation, Inc.: Administrative Records, 1948-1990 (Box 61, Folder 14-15)
  - Men's Benevolent and Social Assocation, Inc.: Centennial Ball, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Men's Benevolent and Social Assocation, Inc.: Dance Programs, 1960, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Men's Benevolent and Social Assocation, Inc.: Photographs, 1963, undated (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Sash, undated (Box 21)
- XIX. Longford, 1989-2006
  - Annual Dinner Dance Program, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Dinner Dance, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - County Longford Association / Social Club of New York St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - County Longford Assocation St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - County Longford Assocation St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - County Longford Assocation St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - County Longford Social Club Dance Videos, 1991-1992; 2 videocassettes (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - County Longford Social Club Dance Videos, 1995; 2 videocassettes (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Dinner Dance Program, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 8-9)
  - Dinner Dance Program, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Dinner Dance, 1957-1973 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Dinner Dance, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Dinner Dance, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Dinner Dance, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 3-4)
  - Dinner Dance, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Dinner Dance, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Dinner Dance, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Dinner Dance, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Dinner Dance, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Dinner Dance, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Dinner Dance, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Dinner Dance, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Dinner Dance, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Dinner Dance, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Dinner Dance, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Dinner Dance, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Dinner Dance, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Dinner Dance, 2011 (Box 47, Folder 8-9)
  - Dinner Dance, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
  - Dinner Dance, 2014 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Dinner Dance, 2016 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Dinner Dance, 2017 (Box 48, Folder 5-6)
  - Dinner Dance, 2018 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - 1798-1998 Commemoration of Battle of Ballinamuck (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Booklets, Cards, Ephemera, 1998-2012 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - County Longford Association 100th Anniversary, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - County Longford Association Newsletters, 1994-2016 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Father John Drumgoole, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - History -- General, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 49, Folder 3-5)
  - History -- Arnold Meagher's Book, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - History -- History of Killoe, circa 1990s (Box 49, Folder 7-8)
  - Irish Brigade Sargeant Bernard Connolly, circa 1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Longford Association of Greater New York, 2008-2009 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Longford Pipe Band Visit to New York, 1994-1996 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Monsignor Bernard Corrigan (Chaplain for Longford Association), 2011-2013 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1996-2017 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - People of Note, 2007-2013 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Pope John Paul II, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - St. Patrick's Day, 1989-2012 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Taoiseach Albert Reynolds, 1996-2014 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Requiem Mass for John Curry, 2017 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- XX. Louth, 1956-2001
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Annual Ball, 1951-1952 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Annual Ball, 1954-1956 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Annual Ball, 1958-1959, 1961-1963 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Annual Ball, 1964-1967 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Annual Ball, 1968, 1974, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Annual Ball, 1996-2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Annual Ball, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc.: Golden Jubilee Banquet, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Minutes, 1975-1984 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Football, 1958-1979 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- XXI. Mayo, 1924-2006
  - Bohola: Its History and Its People, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Erris Association of America, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - GAA Diary of a Century: A Chronicle of Events in Mayo and Elsewhere, 1885-1984 by Johnny Mulvey, after 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Costume, undated (Box 26)
  - Mayo Association: Ball, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Mayo Association: Yearbook, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Association: Yearbook, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Association: Yearbook, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Football Club of New York Annual Reunion and Dance, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mayo Gaelic Football Club of Greater New York Annual Dinner Dance, 2000, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Mayo Ladies Auxiliary: Annual Ball, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Ladies Auxiliary, Our Lady of Knock: Silk Banner, circa 1945; cuid36285 (Box 27)
  - Mayo Men's Benevolent and Patriotic Association: Constitution and by-laws, 1902 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Men's Committee for the Election of O'Dwyer - Joseph and Impellitteri: Contributions, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Applications, 1940-1951 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Banners, Undated; cuid856; 2 items two banners (Roll-storage AIA.003.cuid856)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Centennial Yearbook, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Constitution, circa 1984 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Financial Ledger, 1936-1955 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Financial Ledgers, 1938-1963 (Box 17)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Financial Ledger, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 4, 1924 - Apr 12, 1927; cuid816 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York Meeting Minutes, May 10, 1927 - Dec 9, 1930; cuid817 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 31, 1931-Dec 12, 1933; cuid818 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 23, 1934-Dec 10, 1935; cuid819 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 14, 1936-Jul 12, 1938; cuid820 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Membership Ledger, 1940-1945 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Membership Ledger, 1945-1948 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Membership Ledger, 1961-1970 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Membership Ledger, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association Diamond Jubilee, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 7, Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York Annual Ball, 1965-1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York Annual Fall Dance and Ball and Dinner-Dance, 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Association of New York: Seal, undated (Box 19)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1994, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner souvenir journal, 2015 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Society of New York: By-Laws, Correspondence, 1992, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Society of New York Hibernians of the Year, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Society of New York Michael Davitt and America, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mayo Society of New York Newsletter, 1999, 2006-2009 (Box 11, Folder 8, Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Mayo Society of Philadelphia: 94th Annual Ball, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Mayo Society of Philadelphia: "100 Years of Memories", 2005; TW_AIA_003_ER_1
  - Unidentified Association Ledger (on United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 608 ledger), circa 1947-1953 (Box 16)
  - Panoramic Photograph: Mass and Communion Breakfast of Mayo Ladies Auxiliary, Mayo Men's P & B Association, and May Football Club at teh Hotel Commodore, May 14, 1950 (Box Shared Tamiment AIAXOS001, Folder 2)
- XXII. Meath, 1996
  - The Meath Association, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- XXIII. Monaghan, 1948-2010
  - Administrative Records and Photographs, 1958-1993 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - I Heard They Went to New York exhibit poster, 2008 (Box Shared Tamiment 031, Folder 10)
  - Monaghan Football Club of New York, 1977, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Monaghan Society Sash, undated (Box 22)
  - Terri Connolly Cook Monaghan Society materials, 1948-2010 (Box 28, Folder 4-11, Box Shared Tamiment 031, Folder 6-9)
- XXIX. Offaly, 1965-1999
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Anniversary Dinner Dance Program and Photographs, 1948-1968, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Anniversary Dinner Dance, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc: Annivesary Dinner Dance, 1988-1996 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Banquet, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Dinner Dance, 1982, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Dinner Dance, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Offaly Hurling and Football Club: 7th Annual St. Patrick Ball photograph, 1965 (Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 13)
  - Offaly Social and Athletic Club: Annual Dances, 1938, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Photograph: Hurling Team: Champions 1925-1928 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Photograph: Offaly St Patrick's Celebration (27th Annual), Mar 17, 1952 (Box Shared Tamiment AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
- XXV. Roscommon, 1931-2001
  - Administrative Records, 1955-1966 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - County Roscommon Society Constitution and By-laws, 1948, 1960, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Corporation Papers, 1951-1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Financial: Auditor's Report, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Financial: Cancelled Cheques, 1939-1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jan 1954-Sep 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jun 1965-Feb 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Mar 1974-Dec 1989 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jan 1991-Jan 1994 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Financial: Check Books, 1947-1956 (Box 11a)
  - Financial: Chemical Bank Account, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Financial Correspondence St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Financial Correspondence St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1951-1953 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)